MJ Dashtaki

Senior Frontend Developer

mjd.prg@gmail.com +4915752945752 Germany, Cologne

With over 10 years of experience and a strong technical skill set. My commitment to continuous learning and development has allowed me to contribute significantly to various projects, driving substantial improvements in performance and user experience.

Career Experience

epilot GmbH, Cologne Senior Frontend Developer August 2021 — Present

- Contributed to the ongoing development and enhancement of micro-frontend applications for the digital energy platform, aka e-pilot 360, within the serverless AWS environment
- Creation of self-service portals for end-users from the scratch, <u>Customer/Installer Portals</u> (High impact on company's MRR)
- Enhancing the features also in **optimization**, troubleshooting, and **performance tuning**(400% improvement)
- Collaborated closely with cross-functional team members to enhance the product's architecture and refine engineering practices

React, Svelte, AWS, Typescript, Jest, Playwright, Storybook, GraphQL, monorepo, React-query, RFC, API-first, OpenApi

Azolver, Tallinn, Estonia Senior Frontend Developer

July 2020 — August 2021

- Led the development of TRAX, a web-based tracking system, from inception to launch
- Onboarded and mentored new team members, fostering a culture of continuous learning and improvement
- Participated in the product and technical road map and being involved in the development and implementation of the enterprise applications
- Built efficient and reusable front-end systems and abstractions
- Platform implementation for both web (Angular) and mobile (Ionic)

Angular, Ionic, Azure, Jasmine, Ionic

Devolon, Tartu, Estonia Senior Software Developer

August 2019 — June 2020

- Worked on Fixura, A service for connecting investors and private persons in need for financing
- Contributed to an application named Lentoparkki that scan car license plate and grant a parking lot
- Partnered closely with platform product owners, UX, A/B testing, digital marketing, and the IT department to ensure organizational alignment and acceptance
- Created product features and platform improvements and also writing behavior tests

React, NodeJS, JavaScript

Sava Arman Kish, Tehran, Iran Senior Frontend Developer

June 2017 — July 2019

- Shaped and led the team of frontend developers of Bitex, a cryptocurrency exchange platform
- Optimized the application for maximum speed and scalability
- Established project priorities, deadlines, and deliverables

- Resolved workflow conflicts between the design team, back-end team, and other FE developers.
- Created high-quality, documented, and maintainable code that is used throughout engineering.

Angular, RxJS, Jenkins, SASS, NgRx, Open API, Jenkins

Rayvarz Software Engineering, Tehran, Iran Senior Frontend Developer

July 2012 — June 2018

- Developed HR platforms and internal tools for enterprise clients
- Created multiple internal tools names Double, a tool for Record, replay, and stub HTTP interactions
- Conducted code reviews and implemented testing strategies to maintain code quality and reliability
- Developed and maintain custom CSS framework named Pretty based on Bootstrap and Metronic Admin Theme
- Modified and Enhanced open source Javascript/AngularJS projects such as maskInput, persianDatepicker, selectizeJS
- Full software lifecycle, including the interpretation of requirements, unit, integration, and E2E testing, and the CI/CD pipeline

AngularJS, SASS, JavaScript, Mocha, Chai, Galen, Karma, Bootstrap, SVN

Parsan Web Co., Tehran, Iran Web Application Developer

February 2011 — June 2012

- Designed and developed content management systems
- Created custom plugins and extensions

C#, .Net, CSS, HTML, jQuery

Dorsa Group Co., Tehran, Iran UI Designer

August 2006 — July 2007

Contributed on implementing a document management system

C#, .Net

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Software Azad University, Tehran, Iran

Associate's Degree in Computer Software Azad University, Tehran, Iran

Github - Linkedin